http://www.globalrubber.com/contact/privacy-policy

We at Global Rubber Products Ltd. are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information ("Personal Information") you share with us.Personal Information means any information that may be used to identify an individual, including, but not limited to, a first and last name, a home or other physical address, an e-mail address or other contact information, whether at work or at home. In general, you can visit Global Rubber Products Ltd. web pages without telling us who you are or revealing any Personal Information about yourself.We do not collect “cookies”, if you choose to provide us with your Personal Information on the web, we will transfer that information, within Global Rubber Products Ltd. only.
Personal information will be used to provide our Internet visitors with appropriate product information via the registered email address. Global Rubber Products Ltd. will not market, sell or license our visitor’s information to parties or individuals outside of Global Rubber Products Ltd.Global Rubber Products Ltd. strives to comply with all applicable laws around the globe that are designed to protect your privacy. Although legal requirements may vary from country to country, Global Rubber Products Ltd. intends to adhere to the principles set forth in this Online Privacy Policy. In other words, our goal is to provide protection for your Personal Information no matter where that personal information is collected, transferred or retained.
Copyright Global Rubber Products Ltd 2020 - Legal
Created by
Legal notice
